americaas insist on being first in
everything first in wealth first in
military might first in the buffet line
first in cholesterol but since we don't
innovate anything important anymore we
now put most of our brain power into
devising increasingly insane food stuffs
that we can shove in our Patriot holes
which of these is a new real food you
can actually buy at an American Ballpark
a funnel cake sandwich with barbecue
pulled pork fried onions shredded
cheddar monter jack cheese bacon in a
jalapeno skewer everyone just got
diarrhea hearing that you
just just I should have given you Pepto
before I even read that or a deep fried
meatball sub on a glazed Cronut bun
called the hogy
Bea one of those is real Christen Shaw
they're both they're both pretty good
options but I'm going to go with the
hogy be uh that actually sounds like the
good one it's not it's the first one is
real Yep this is H Kansas City's Koffman
Stadium now offering the pulled pork
patty melt a deep fried mass that if you
squint I'm pretty sure looks like guy
Fier with a shirt
off and his little bacon
arms it's
a it's the the first the first ever food
modeled on the cancer it
causes this is what get remov for
that it should have a little Mountaineer
on the side of
it
Ying up the side you know there's just
there's just camps of people who
couldn't make it to the
top and and an obese guy at the bottom
eating a small version of one of
them
[Applause]
exactly